[
  {
    "id":1,
    "question":"How many sisters does Joey have?",
    "options":[5,6,7,8],
    "answer":1
  },
    {
    "id":2,
    "question":"What’s Phoebe’s sister’s name?",
    "options":["ariel","monica","ursula","rachel"],
    "answer":2
  },
    {
    "id":3,
    "question":"What’s Joey’s favorite food?",
    "options":["pizza","sandwich","lasagne","donut"],
    "answer":1
  },
  {
    "id":4,
    "question":"How many times has Ross been married?",
    "options":[1,2,3,4],
    "answer":2
  },
    {
    "id":5,
    "question":"What was the name of the comic book Ross made when he was young?",
    "options":["science boy","game boy","mommy's boy","super boy"],
    "answer":0
  },
    {
    "id":6,
    "question":"Where did Rachel, Monica and Ross go to high school?",
    "options":["Lincoln High","Washington High","Central High","Western High"],
    "answer":0
  },
    {
    "id":7,
    "question":"Where does Chandler move to in season nine?",
    "options":["Boston","Washington","Tulsa","London"],
    "answer":2
  },
    {
    "id":8,
    "question":"Who does Gunther have a crush on?",
    "options":["Monica","Rachel","Phoebe","Joey"],
    "answer":1
  },
    {
    "id":9,
    "question":"What is Monica allergic to?",
    "options":["Cat hair","Mouse","Monkey hair","Dog hair"],
    "answer":3
  },
    {
    "id":10,
    "question":"Which soap opera did Joey have a role on?",
    "options":["Dr.Drake Ramoray","General Hospital","New Amsterdam","Days of our lives"],
    "answer":3
  }
]